- Amy, you look great.
- l know.
(Leonard:)Where'd you get a beer?
(Raj:)From that happy young couple over there
with all the tattoos.
(Raj:)Beautiful story. They're in rival
drug gangs and they're getting married.
(Raj:)Shh. No one can know.
(Amy:)Look at all these people in love.
(Amy:)Kind of gets you thinking, doesn't it?
(Sheldon:)It does, indeed.
(Sheldon:)Leonard, is it awkward
being here with Penny...
(Sheldon:)...given that you recently
proposed to her?
- You proposed?
- l don't wanna talk about it.
Where'd he pop the question?
What'd you say?
- She said no. Can we drop it?
- It wasn't a real proposal.
- Why wasn't it a real proposal?
- He asked her during coitus.
(Howard:)Did you get down on one knee
or were you already there? Ha, ha!